Guide to the Richard Pommer Papers MC 125
New York University Archives
- Series I: Papers
  - 20th-Century Architecture: Museum Design Seminar *Box 17 also contains a small box of bibliographic topics and citations as well as two rolls of microfilm: Creese, Walter L. American Architecture from 1918-1933 with Special Emphasis on European Influence. Harvard University dissertation, 1949; Syracuse University, George Arents Library, assorted magazine articles, photographs and scrapbook entries., 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)